## **Spiros Xiarchos**

Information Systems Specialist

Email: contact@xiarchos.gr Web: sp.xiarchos.gr

## About Me

Hey there, I'm Spiros and I am an undergraduate student in the Department of Informatics of the Ionian University.

My interests include, but are not limited to, gaining experience in the following areas:

- Networking (Firewalling, SDWAN)
- Web development (e.g. React or Angular)
- E-shop Frameworks (e.g. WooCommerce or Magento)
- Mobile development (iOS only)
- End-to-end testing suites (e.g. puppeteer)

Technical skills are not the only area I have developed through my expirience. My peers describe me as a valuable team member, who knows how to work under strict deadlines and provide quality results.

## Education

# B.Sc.

Ionian University, Corfu GR

01/10/2015 -Present Specialization in Information Systems.

#### Main courses follow:

- Electronic Commerce/Information
   Systems and Supply Management
- Analysis and Design of Information Systems/Strategic Management of Information Systems
- Software, Application,
   Communications and Network
   Security/Information System
   Security Managment
- Information Privacy Policies and Enhancing Technologies/Social and Legal Issues of ICTs

## Experience

## Network Administrator

Intercompass MPD, Glyfada GR 01/06/2022 -Present

Network
Managment/
NET 7, Corfu
CHUSTOMER
Support

- Network Design, Deployment and Administration (Mikrotik/Cisco).
- System Operations Assitant (WHM CPanel/Direct Admin/Microsoft 365/Proxmox/Synology/ NextCLoud/OSTicket System/ SnipelT).
- WISP Network Manager (Ubiquiti/ Mikrotik)
- Customer Support Manager (UISP CRM)

## Network Managment/ IT Support

Messinian Networks, Kalamata GR

23/06/2016 -30/11/2022

- 23/06/2016 31/08/2016: Training on Network Installations and IT Support (Kalamata). (Mikrotik/ Ubiquiti)
- 01/09/2016 20/06/2021: B2B IT Support and Network Managment (Corfu). (Mikrotik/Synology/ VMware)
- 21/06/2021 30/11/2022: Network Management and Customer Support Service (Kalamata). (UISP CRM/NMS) (Hybrid)

## A Little More About Me

Apart from my job's related interests I'm keen on:

- Traveling
- · Audiophilism and Vinyl Records
- MotoGP

Spiros Xiarchos - contact@xiarchos.gr